Guide to the The Ewing Family Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Presley K. Ewing
  - Correspondence
    - Business
      - J.H. Whitney
        - To Mrs. M. H. Throckmorton re: June’s Address, June 24, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 166)
        - From J. H. Whitney re: Financials, June 13, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 167)
      - Various
        - From Physical Culture Corporation re: MacFadden Letter, December 30-31, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 168)
        - To the National Bank of Commerce re: Lee Tire & Service Company, October 25, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 169)
        - To D.A. Schulte, Inc. re: Binz Building Lease, February 26, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 170)
        - To E.J. Peters, City Ticket Agent re: Payment, June 4, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 171)
        - To The New Majestic re: Payment for Seats, January 25, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 172)
        - To Mutual Life Insurance Company re: Policy Loans, May 30, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 173)
        - To American Express Company re: Mail, May 30, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 174)
        - To Westheimer Warehouse Co., Inc. re: Payment, May 4, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 175)
        - To I.P. Walker, Manager GA Stowers Furniture Co. re: Credit, June 3, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 176)
        - To J.W. Northrop, Jr. re: Basin and Lights, June 5, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 177)
        - To William Trueheart re: Dancing Lessons, July 15, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 178)
      - Winthrop Furniture Co.
        - re: Delivery, May 27, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 179)
        - re: Furniture Purchase, June 3, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 180)
      - Woodburn American Railway Co.
        - From A.J. Rowell re: Painting, May 22, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 181)
        - From W.S. Woodburn American Railway Co. re: Painting, June 2, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 182)
    - Christmas Cards
      - From Eunice, undated (Box 1, Folder 183)
      - From Willie, undated (Box 1, Folder 184)
      - From Sam Streetman, undated (Box 1, Folder 185)
      - From Mr. & Mrs. W.M. Sweeney, Dec 19, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 186)
    - Family
      - Abbott C. Combes
        - re: Proposition, December 24, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - re: Proposal to Gladys (daughter), undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Cousins
        - From Lucy E. Lee Ewing re: General, January 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - To Miss Lucy E. Lee Ewing re: Presley’s Book, January 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - To Miss Leila A. Green re: Cousin Fannie, June 4, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - From Mrs. T.B. Kittredge re: Marriage, May 28, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - From Mrs. T.B. Kittredge re: General, December 10, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - From Mrs. T.B. Kittredge re: Best Wishes, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - To Mrs. Fannie Adele Payne re: General, June 5, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - C.W. Veatch
        - Telegram to Mr. C.W. Veatch re: Dinner, February 2, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence Between C.W. Veatch and Stella Erhardt re: Lots for Sale, July 6, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - To the National Bank of Commerce re: Lee Tire & Service Company, January 13, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Enid Cary
        - re: General, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - re: Sewanee, May 19, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - re: Winthrop Furniture Company, December 14, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Fayette C. Ewing
        - re: Illness, December 10, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - re: Pardons, April 30, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        - re: Birthday, July 20, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        - re: Birthday, July 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - re: Ku Klux Klan, August 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - re: Judge Barclay, October 1, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - re: Judge Barclay, December 9, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - re: Dogs, February 21, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - re: Visit, February 27, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - re: Visit, March 6, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - re: Judge Lamb, June 2, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - re: Family, June 18, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - re: General, July 7, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - re: Birthday, July 21, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Gladys Ewing Combes
        - re: Trip, April 14, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        - re: Rental Property, September 1, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - re: Arrival, January 4, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - re: Victory, March 4, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 33)
        - re: Wedding, June 8, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - re: Best Wishes, June 12, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - re: Castlewood Management, September 11, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 36)
        - re: Financials, November 22, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 37)
        - re: Roy H. Palmer, Assistant Director, Chief Audit Division, Income Tax Bureau, January 8, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 38)
        - re: Carleton, January 18, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 39)
        - re: Visit, January 8, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 40)
        - re: Visit and Carleton, January 9, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 41)
        - re: Fee Payments, February 28, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 42)
        - re: Trip to Europe, April 18, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 43)
        - re: Travel on the Minnetonka, April 24, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 44)
        - re: Trip to Europe, May 17, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 45)
        - re: Travel Itinerary, May 23, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 46)
        - re: Trip to Europe, May 26, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 47)
        - re: Trip to Europe, June 4, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 48)
        - re: Trip with Kittredge, October 28, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 49)
        - re: Financials, January 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - re: St. Louis, January 5, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        - re: New House, April 8, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 52)
        - re: Family Issues, April 17, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 53)
        - re: Gladys’s Birthday, April 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 54)
        - re: Family Issues, April 28, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 55)
        - re: Family Issues, May 13, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 56)
        - re: Family Issues, May 27, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 57)
        - re: Damaged Paintings, June 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 58)
        - re: Damaged Paintings, June 3, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 59)
        - re: Portrait Repairer, June 3, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 60)
        - re: Damaged paintings, June 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 61)
        - re: Damage to Portraits, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
        - re: Portrait Appraisal, June 8, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 63)
        - re: Wire Received, June 8, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - re: Pets, June 17, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 65)
        - re: “The House Next Door”, June 26, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 66)
        - re: Family Issues, July 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 67)
        - re: Family Issues, July 9, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 68)
        - re: Legal Claim, July 15, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 69)
        - re: Best Wishes, July 20, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 70)
        - re: Birthday, July 21, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - re: Family Issues, July 31, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 72)
        - re: Family Issues, September 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        - re: Family Issues, September 15, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - re: Dogs, September 24, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 75)
        - re: Arrival in Pennsylvania, October 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 76)
        - re: Greeting, October 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 77)
        - re: Family Issues, October 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 78)
        - re: Family Issues, November 11, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 79)
        - re: Family Issues, November 18, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 80)
        - re: Family Issues, November 24, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 81)
        - re: Family Issues, December 4, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 82)
        - re: Financials, December 8, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 83)
        - re: Family Issues, December 15, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 84)
        - re: Visit, December 22, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 85)
        - re: Family Issues, February 4, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 86)
        - re: Foley & Geary Cases, February 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 87)
        - re: Family Issues, February 20, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 88)
        - re: Family Issues, February 26, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 89)
        - re: Family Picture, March 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 90)
        - re: Illness of Abbott III (son), April 1, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 91)
        - re: Castlewood Dividend, April 7, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 92)
        - re: Illness of Abbott III (son), April 16, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 93)
        - re: Family, May 4, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 94)
        - re: Family Issues, June 23, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 95)
        - re: Family Issues, July 7, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 96)
        - re: Birthday, July 21, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 97)
        - re: Illness, July 26, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 98)
        - re: General/ Mention of Spindletop, July 30, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 99)
        - re: Illness, August 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 100)
        - re: Arrival, August 14, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 101)
        - re: Arrival at Sheffield, August 14, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 102)
        - re: Arrival home, October 23, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 103)
        - re: Children’s Clothes, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
        - re: Christmas, undated (Box 2, Folder 105)
        - re: Christmas, undated (Box 2, Folder 106)
        - re: Financials, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
        - re: Visit, undated (Box 2, Folder 108)
        - re: Well Wishes, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
      - Grandchildren
        - From Presley Vinson re: General, July 19, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 110)
        - From Kittredge Vinson re: General, July 20, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 111)
        - From Kittredge Vinson re: General, August 29, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 112)
        - To Kittredge Vinson re: Allowance, May 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 113)
        - To Kittredge Vinson re: Allowance, April 29, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 114)
        - To Abbott Combes, III re: Pets, March 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 115)
        - From Abbott Combes, III, re: Christmas, undated (Box 2, Folder 116)
        - To Abbott and Mary Ellen Combes re: Birthday, July 21, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - June Ewing
        - re: Birthday, July 21, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 118)
        - re: Illness, undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
        - From William Clark re: Husband’s Death, February 10, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 120)
      - Leila Werlein
        - re: General News, undated (Box 2, Folder 121)
        - re: Mother’s Estate, Dec 22, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 122)
        - re: A Dream, April 18, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 123)
        - re: Passport, April 24, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 124)
        - re: Passport, June 4, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 125)
        - re: Illness, July 21, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 126)
        - re: Illness/Birthday, July 27, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 127)
      - Rev. Quincy Ewing
        - re: Family, August 7, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 128)
        - re: Laws Concerning Criminal Conspiracies, May 14, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 129)
        - re: Gubernatorial Clemency/Europe Trip, June 4, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 130)
        - re: Forth Deaths, June 6, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 131)
        - re: Ku Klux Klan, November 10, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 132)
        - re: Illness, December 8, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 133)
        - re: Saints, March 30, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 134)
        - re: Correspondence, April 7, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 135)
        - re: Religion, April 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 136)
        - re: Family Issues, May 6, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 137)
        - re: Gladys, May 26, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 138)
        - re: Trip to Houston, July 9, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 139)
        - re: Picture of June, July 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 140)
        - re: Trip to Houston, July 28, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 141)
        - re: Bible in School, July 30, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 142)
        - re: Ku Klux Klan, August 5, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 143)
        - re: Miracles, September 26, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 144)
        - re: M.E. Foster, October 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 145)
        - re: Letter in The States, October 31, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 146)
        - re: Family Issues, December 9, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 147)
        - re: Religious Philosophy, December 28, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 148)
        - re: Sugar Crop, January 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 149)
        - re: Gladys and Vesta, January 15, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 150)
        - re: Cane Farming, January 28, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 151)
        - re: Loan, January 30, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 152)
        - re: Release of a Security, February 3, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 153)
        - re: Debt Repayment, February 5, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 154)
        - re: Farm Issues, February 10, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 155)
        - re: Dogs/Loan, March 6, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 156)
        - re: Re-inscription of Loan, March 22, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 157)
        - re: General, March 23, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 158)
        - re: General, April 22, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 159)
        - re: Birthday/General, July 23, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 160)
        - re: Literature, August 4, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 161)
        - re: Ponzi Case, August 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 162)
      - Vesta Ewing Veatch
        - re: Past Due or Old Accounts, undated (Box 2, Folder 163)
        - re: Dodge car, August 7, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 164)
        - re: General, May 12, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 165)
        - re: General, May 25, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 166)
      - Family History
        - From Mrs. Harry E. Thixton re: Genealogy, July 14, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 167)
        - From Edward Adams re: Genealogy, April 14, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 168)
        - From W.M. Crook re: Career, June 12, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 169)
        - To W.M. Crook re: Biographical Sketch, June 15, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 170)
        - From Mrs. Octavia Boud re: Genealogy, October 1, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 171)
        - To Mrs. Charles F. Ratcliff re: Genealogy, September 9, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 172)
        - From Henry B. Williams re: Inquiry of Family, January 11, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 173)
        - To Henry B. Williams re: Family, January 16, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Hotels
      - To W.E. Ratliffe-Hotel Van Nuys, June 6, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 175)
      - Lankershim Hotel-Los Angeles, California, May 30, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 176)
      - Hotel Beaumont-Beaumont, Texas, January 11, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 177)
      - Adlon Hotel-Berlin, Germany, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 178)
      - Agnello and Du Dome Hotel-Milan, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 179)
      - Amstel Hotel-Amsterdam, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 180)
      - Astoria Hotel-Brussels, Belgium, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 181)
      - Barbensi (Pension)-Florence, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 182)
      - Bonini-Milan, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 183)
      - Bristol Hotel-Berlin, Germany, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 184)
      - Brock’s Doelen Hotel-Amsterdam, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 185)
      - Eden Hotel-Rome, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 186)
      - Elysee Hotel-Rome, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 187)
      - Esplanade Hotel-Berlin, Germany, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 188)
      - Florin Hotel-Rome, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 189)
      - Grand Hotel-Brussels, Belgium, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 190)
      - Grand Hotel-Vienna, Austria, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 191)
      - Hotel D’Albion-Florence, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 192)
      - Hotel Castille-Paris, France, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 193)
      - Hotel Matigon-Paris, France, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 194)
      - Hotel Van Nuys-Los Angeles, California, May 30, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 195)
      - National Hotel-Lucerne, Switzerland, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 196)
      - North British Hotel-Edinburgh, Scotland, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 197)
      - Palace Hotel-Lucerne, Switzerland, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 198)
      - Queen’s Hotel-Antwerp, Belgium, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 199)
      - Regina Hotel-Paris, France, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 200)
      - Regina Hotel-Venice, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 201)
      - Savoia and Jolanda Hotel-Paris, France, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 202)
      - Savoia and Jolanda Hotel-Venice, Italy, May 30, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 203)
      - Negresco Hotel-Nice, France, June 2, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 204)
      - O’Connor Hotel-Nice, France, June 2, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 205)
      - Prince De Galles Hotel-Monte Carlo, Monaco, June 2, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 206)
      - Des Indes Hotel-The Hague, June 3, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 207)
      - Paulez Hotel-The Hague, June 3, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 208)
      - To Miss Stella Erhardt-Touraine Hotel re: Weeds, October 30, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Legal Cases
      - American Sulphur Royalty Co. of Texas
        - To A.E. Vorderman, January 10, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 210)
        - To H.T. Staiti, June 4, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 211)
      - D.R. Beatty
        - re: Peggy Griffith, May 2, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 212)
        - From J.H. Whitney re: Peggy Griffith, May 2, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 213)
        - To Mrs. P.J. (Peggy) Griffith re: D.R. Beatty, May 2, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 214)
        - re: Peggy Griffith, May 2, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 215)
      - Galveston Causeway
        - From O.W. Terry re: Causeway Case, February 15, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 216)
        - To William Stansbury, June 6, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 217)
        - To William Stansbury re: Thank You, June 9, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 218)
        - From William Stansbury re: Opinion, June 9, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 219)
        - re: Petition for Certiorari, June 9, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 220)
        - To West Publishing Company re: Petition for Certiorari, June 11, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 221)
        - To William Stansbury re: Opinion, June 14, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 222)
      - Joe H. Eagle
        - re: Norvell v. Beatty, February 19, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 223)
        - re: Norvell v. Beatty, May 12, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 224)
      - James Ferguson
        - re: Thomas Davis Estate, July 23, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 225)
        - re: Thank You, July 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 226)
        - re: Position on Texas Supreme Court, August 19, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 227)
        - re: Position on Texas Supreme Court, August 22, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 228)
      - W.L. Marbury
        - re: Mound Company Lease, November 28, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 229)
        - re: Mound Company Lease, January 25, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 230)
        - re: Lanahan & Grieske v. Welch, February 5, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 231)
      - Anita B. Stewart
        - re: Claim Against John S. Stewart Estate, January 15, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 232)
        - re: Claim Against John S. Stewart Estate, January 30, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 233)
      - Daniel Walker
        - re: Opinion, March 1, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 234)
        - re: Opinion, March 5, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 235)
        - re: Legal Case, July 22, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 236)
        - re: Legal Case, July 25, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 237)
      - Various
        - From A.H. Willie, Chief Justice Supreme Court of Texas, December 5, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 238)
        - From Marie K. MacLean re: Will, March 7, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 239)
        - From George W. Graves re: Legal Case, January 29, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 240)
        - To Devaille H. Theard re: Albert Smith Case, May 5, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 241)
        - To E.W. Tucker re: Bad Check, May 9, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 242)
    - Love Letters
      - To Unknown, undated (Box 2, Folder 243)
      - From Blanche Wallace re: Ring, undated (Box 2, Folder 244)
      - To Blanche Wallace re: Ring, April 3, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 245)
    - Ministers
      - A.A. McKenzie
        - re: Record of Baptism, April 24, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 246)
      - Charles Clingman
        - re: Health of Wife (Mary Ellen), April 9, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 247)
        - re: Letter of Transfer, June 11, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 248)
        - re: Letter of Transfer, June 27 1923 (Box 2, Folder 249)
      - Hunter Lewis
        - re: Junior Service League, April 5, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 250)
        - re: Junior Service League, April 10, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 251)
        - re: Donation, April 23, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 252)
        - re: Water Supply, May 30, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 253)
        - re: Water Supply, June 23, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 254)
        - re: Donation-Rectory, July 21, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 255)
        - re: Rectory Roof, July 24, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 256)
        - re: Thank You-Donation, July 31, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 257)
      - Peter Sears
        - re: General, April 5, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 258)
        - re: Ku Klux Klan, August 5, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 259)
        - re: General, April 7, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 260)
        - re: Illness, November 6, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 261)
    - Personal
      - William Jennings Bryan
        - re: YMCA, December 31, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 262)
        - re: Visit to Houston/Gladys, January 5, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 263)
        - re: Visit to Houston, January 8, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 264)
        - re: Visit to Houston, March 14, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 265)
        - re: Condolences on Death, July 27, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 266)
      - Edna Kennedy Davis
        - re: Thank You, undated (Box 2, Folder 267)
        - re: Marriage, undated (Box 2, Folder 268)
        - re: Baby Gift, undated (Box 2, Folder 269)
      - M.E. Foster
        - re: Mrs. Ewing (Presley’s mother), March 31, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 270)
        - re: James Ferguson, August 24, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 271)
        - re: Appointment to Texas Supreme Court, August 26, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 272)
        - re: Quincy’s Articles, October 23, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 273)
        - re: Quincy’s Articles, October 27, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 274)
        - re: Quincy’s Articles, November 5, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 275)
        - re: Quincy’s Articles, November 6, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 276)
      - Ruth LaVelle
        - re: Payment, December 25, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 277)
        - re: Article in Houston Chronicle, April 11, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 278)
      - Mortimer Lewis
        - re: Poem, July 2, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 279)
        - re: “Fairy Ways”, June 22, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 280)
      - Judge Norman Kittrell
        - re: Amnesty Bill, March 7, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 281)
        - re: Norman’s Picture, October 23 & November 2, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 282)
      - Joseph Tumulty, Secretary to the President
        - re: Thank You, December 27, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 283)
        - re: Thank You, October 11, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 284)
      - Various
        - Telegram to Sgt. Carlton Veatch, June 4, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 285)
        - To Capt. Ewing Werlein re: Legal Case, October 8, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 286)
        - From Otto Faub re: Best Wishes, August 22, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 287)
        - Janvier Wedding Invitation, May 23, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 288)
        - From J.B. Gork, M.D. re: Insomnia, June 8, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 289)
        - To Maria E. Martin re: Picture of Thomas Ewing, June 16, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 290)
        - To Mrs. R.E. Fleig re: Best Wishes, August 6, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 291)
        - To Florence Eldridge re: Illness, August 7, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 292)
        - To Miss Mary Gibson Kirby re: General, August 7, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 293)
        - From Arthur Crownover re: General, August 26, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 294)
        - To Frank Clemens re: New Year’s, January 5, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 295)
        - From Thomas [?] re: General, From Thomas [?] re: General, January 9, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 296)
        - To Katherine Stevens re: Trip to New Orleans, April 28, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 297)
        - From Rowena A. Clark re: Marriage, August 1, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 298)
        - To C.P. Shearn re: Mrs. Christie, June 5, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 299)
        - To Dr. Knickerbocker re: Poem, undated (Box 2, Folder 300)
        - From R.S. re: General, undated (Box 2, Folder 301)
        - To Mrs. Addison (Anne Payne Hargis) Rogers re: Death of Mary Ellen, March 17, ____ (Box 2, Folder 302)
    - Politics
      - Local
        - From Clarence R. Wharton re: Paving and Widening of Clay Avenue, May 9, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 303)
        - To Clarence R. Wharton re: Paving and Widening of Clay venue, May 26, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 304)